dvdstyler.org 2011-02-17

# Privacy Policy

Free DVD authoring and burning tool for Linux and Windows

This privacy policy sets out how Thüring IT-Consulting uses and protects any information that you give Thüring IT-Consulting when you use this website.

Thüring IT-Consulting is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Thüring IT-Consulting may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01.01.2011.

**What we collect**

On our website, we use the open source web analysis software Piwik. Data collected by Piwik includes IP, time and duration of the visit, what pages are visited, used browser and plugins, search-engines and referrer. While Piwik uses a cookie to distinguish between individual visitors, the collected data doesn't allow to identify individuals. The collected data will only be used to improve the website - especially that data won't be matched with data from other sources, and we won't share the collected data with third parties. We'll only use anoymized, collective analysis provided by Piwik for our evaluation.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

|   
---|---
